Jamie Joseph Heiney

Controller for Construction Company

About Me

Experienced Controller with a background in managing finance and accounting teams. Proven track record of creating and implementing systems to improve efficiency and accuracy. Strong communication skills with an ability to simplify complex topics for stakeholders at all levels.

Skills

- Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- Simplification of complex topics
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Budgeting and Financial Planning
- Google Sheets
- Excellent communication

Experience

Accountant

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- Managed bookkeeping for several capital funding companies
- Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets and Google App Scripts
- Provided accounting consulting services to multiple companies owned by Alpha Capital

Nursing Home Game Creator

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- · Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities to address the lack of stimulating and engaging content for elders
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes and hundreds of happy users
- · Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management

AP Regional Manager

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017

- · Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff

Education

Certificate - Accounting Foundations Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks Online Essential Training

Diploma - May 2008, 3.4 GPA Dual Enrolment Florida International University

Accounting Course: Accounting Coach course by Harold Averkamp Tested and received

Contact: 305-801-7497